

susan vergnaud

Chicago, IL. 60608 • 773-459-3249

education

Columbia College Chicago

•B.A. Interactive Arts & Media with a concentration in Graphic Design

Digital Bootcamp

•Web Development course

summary

Senior graphic designer and production artist skilled in both print and front end web production. I have worked on posters, postcards, direct mail, brochures, newsprint, flyers, websites, email newsletters and event marketing and signage. I have a great eye for color, typography and layout design. I work quickly and accurately while managing multiple projects, meeting tight deadlines and adhering to brand consistency. My professional background also includes working in fine art/illustration at Gallery 37 as an Apprentice Artist/Teaching Assistant.

skills

- Excellent skills in Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign, Acrobat, Microsoft Office.
- Knowledge of Quark, Dreamweaver, After Effects, Final Cut Pro, PowerPoint, Flash, HTML, CSS.
- Platforms: Windows and Mac OS's.

experience

National Restaurant Assoc. Education Foundation Senior Graphic Designer Chicago, IL 1/2013-current (Freelance)

- Design, edit and layout event marketing/signage, promotional posters, banners, emails, flyers and brochures for their annual nationwide invitational and annual golf classic event.
- Create various foundation and event logos for print and web use.
- Manage and track progress of multiple projects and keep up with various editing rounds.
- Work with the internal marketing communications team to revise and create all foundation materials regarding these two annual events.

Shared Marketing Services 9/2006-1/2013

Senior Graphic Designer

Chicago, IL

- Designed, edited and laid out web banners, emails, magazine ads, newsprint, brochures, promotional posters, postcards, logo design, flyers, icons, letterheads for various client/dealer advertising campaians.
- Retouched, color corrected images, managed asset library and converted PDF files to jpegs.
- Edited animation, video, radio advertisements and created Photoshop website mockups.
- •Created guide images for print and HTML templates before being passed to the web dev. team.
- Proof all final print files before being sent out to outside vendors ensuring accuracy.
- Worked with account executives and the web dev. team to finish all the above tasks on time.
- Clients/Dealers included: VW, Audi, Harley Davidson, BP, New Balance, Milgard and Ace Hardware.

Daniel Lamp 2003-2004

Graphic Designer

Chicago, IL

- Responsible for the design and layout of brochures, pamphlets, flyers, catalogs and business cards.
- •Photographed inventory for use in catalog and marketing materials.
- •Created and maintained image assets on the server.
- •Trained employees on various design software.

interests

I like to draw, sketch, paint and do various freelance projects. I am also involved with the Taproot Foundation doing pro bono design work for non for profit organizations.

www.susanvdesign.com • susan.vergnaud@gmail.com • 773.459.3249